<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>54chi</title>
    <description>Thoughts, stories and ideas...but mostly ideas. Mostly around the tech hype of the moment. Now with more AI.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 16:06:30 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 16:06:30 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing Technical Documentation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Another day, another rant. The developers never have the time to jump back from their IDE of choice into Word or PDF editor, and write or update documentation; and sadly most technical writers are not usually involved enough to understand what needs to be documented or how to perform efficiently.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It doesn’t have to be that way. Develepers could (and should) document their code from within their IDEs and as part of their deployment process. It is much useful to keep it as part of their repos, so there is less interruptions by having to switch between something like Atom...</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 11:33:08 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/writing-technical-documentation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/writing-technical-documentation/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        <category>plantuml</category>
        
        <category>asciidoc</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Specs</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been denying this blog for a Year already. Things got busier and I am no longer enjoying a “long vacation”. Because of my current job, a few things have changed. Mostly:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;No more Erlang/Elixir (my current job is Java-like, so I can only focus on NodeJS as a side project for now) :(&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;More DevOps and automation though :), thought it will probably be focused on SalesForce :(&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Vue.js :)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;More IoT stuff :)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;REST services :( (though I will try to blog about GraphQL too. We’ll see)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;As for the environment itself, this is what I’m...</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 15:10:33 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/specs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/specs/</guid>
        
        <category>projectplan</category>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        <category>specs</category>
        
        <category>Hardware</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And...we are still alive</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve meant to do this since the beginning of the Year, but being the eclectic guy I was involved in some AI projects and SalesForce work. For the records, I’m not good at AI yet, and SalesForce “cool factor” is gone (sorry fans of SalesForce), so I didn’t feel like blogging about it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;There is also the blog itself. The previous version was made with a local version of Ghost, but it wasn’t easy to maintain it online (since it was building the HTML offline first). I also learned a few things about SEO and standard Schemas, so I wanted...</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 14:53:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/and-we-are-still-alive/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/and-we-are-still-alive/</guid>
        
        <category>rant</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
